lascana.com 2019-12-10

# LASCANA Privacy Policy

## LASCANA Privacy Statement - Effective Date September 16, 2015

LASCANA has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy and security. This document describes LASCANA’s practices with respect to the collection of user information from this Web site. This document only applies to the LASCANA site www.LASCANA.com. We have taken extra steps to make sure your online shopping experience is the best and is safe and secure.

As a visitor to LASCANA’s web site, www.LASCANA.com, you have the right to understand our information privacy practices prior to providing LASCANA with any of your personal information (Personal information includes information that can be linked to a specific individual, such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address).

By providing you with this Privacy Statement, LASCANA is pledging our continued commitment to protecting the information you provide to us. LASCANA regularly examines our information privacy practices to determine whether we are adhering to the disclosures about the collection, use, sharing, and protection of your personal information made in this privacy statement. 

## Privacy Statement

This LASCANA Privacy Statement discloses the information privacy practices for LASCANA's web sites, http://www.LASCANA.com and [http://m.LASCANA.com](http://m.lascana.com/) ("LASCANA").

## Children’s Privacy

LASCANA does not knowingly collect information provided by children under the age of 13. If that policy changes, LASCANA will obtain consent from a parent or guardian before LASCANA knowingly collects data from anyone under the age of 13.

## Information collected about you

LASCANA collects personal information about you that you specifically and voluntarily provide. Personal information includes information that can identify you as a specific individual, such as your name, mailing address, phone number, or e-mail address. Although you are required to register at LASCANA in order to purchase, your personal information is needed in order to process and fulfill your order requests. Many areas of LASCANA can be accessed without providing any personal information. On all LASCANA pages that collect personal information, we specifically describe what information is required in order to provide you with the product or service you have requested.

LASCANA collects personal information when you:  

• Register at LASCANA   
• LASCANA collects your e-mail address and password when you register at our web site.   
• Complete user profile information   
• LASCANA collects the full name, address, city, state, zip, country, e-mail address, shipping information.  
  This information is stored in the My Account area of LASCANA.   
• Participate in a survey or contests   
• Occasionally, LASCANA may offer our site visitors an opportunity to participate in a survey or contest.  
  Information collected by LASCANA when you participate in a survey or contest may include your full name,  
  e-mail address, and street address.   
• Contact LASCANA   
• LASCANA collects personal information such as your full name, zip code, e-mail address, and/or contact  
  number whenever you submit a question or suggestion, or request assistance with viewing your account,  
  logging on to LASCANA, or accessing your account.   
• Request a catalog   
• LASCANA collects your full name, zip code, e-mail address, and shipping address when you submit a request to receive a catalog.

## Cookies and other web site technologies

Some information is collected automatically every time you visit LASCANA. LASCANA and our third party marketing partner collect information about your computer and assign you "cookies" (small, unique identifier text files) when you visit LASCANA. You do not provide this information—it is collected automatically as a means of supporting your visit to our site. Cookies do not contain any personal information. This anonymous information may be used by our marketing partner to deliver advertisements for products and services tailored to your interests on this site or other sites that you visit.

Most browsers are automatically set to accept cookies but provide features that enable you to be notified when a cookie is to be placed on your browser, decline the cookie, or delete cookies that have been placed on your browser. Most mobile operating systems also provide you an option in the device settings to limit ad tracking associated with your device id. You may also check your web browser’s instructions, help files or privacy documentation for further information. You should be aware, however, that some functions of our website or application may not work or may work slowly if a cookie is refused. This LASCANA cookie may be used to provide enhanced online display advertising tailored to your interests. To opt out of this advertising provided directly by LASCANA, click here. When you access the My Account area of the LASCANA web site, LASCANA requires you to sign in using your e-mail address and password. Once you sign in we record the e-mail address in the cookie file on your computer. We may also record your password in this cookie file. Permanent cookie files remain on your computer's hard drive until you manually delete the file.

## How LASCANA Uses Online Remarketing Campaigns

LASCANA uses remarketing programs allowing us to reach people who previously visited the LASCANA.com website, and match those people with the appropriate message. If you want to opt out of the display of our online advertising, which appears on other Web sites, and which is based on online interactions with LASCANA.com, then please click the preference icon that may appear on such advertising.

For more information about your options regarding the use of data by Google Analytics, please go to: <https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/181881?hl=en> .

We do not respond to web browser “do not track” signals at this time. We await the result of work by the policy community and industry to determine when such a response is appropriate and what form it should take. We do allow you to exercise choice regarding the collection of information by third parties about your online activities over time and across third-party websites or online services for online interest based advertising purposes by going to <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/> or <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/> or [http://www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/). 

For more information on your opt-out choices on your mobile device, please visit the iAd Network Advertising Settings page at <https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT202074> for iOS-based devices and Google’s Ads Settings page at <https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/authenticated> for Android-based devices.

## Computer information

LASCANA collects certain technical information from your computer each time you request a page during a visit to LASCANA. This information is collected from your computer's web browser and may include your IP address, operating system, web browser software (i.e., Google Chrome, Firefox, Safari or Internet Explorer), screen resolution, and referrer web site. Wireless users: Please check with your wireless company if you are using your cellular phone to access the Internet to understand whether personal information may be used to identify you.

## Credit Card Guarantee

Your credit card is protected whenever you make a purchase through LASCANA. If any unauthorized charges appear on your credit card statement within 12 months of your last LASCANA transaction, report this fraud to your credit card provider and contact us immediately by calling [1-888-772-3160](tel:18887223160). Most credit card companies cover all charges resulting from credit card fraud, or may limit your responsibility to $50, the maximum allowed under the Fair Credit Billing Act. LASCANA is committed to making sure you're covered.

## Sharing your information

LASCANA will, on occasion make our mailing list (name and address only) available to select companies whose products might be of interest to you. If you do not wish to receive those mailings or do not wish to receive our catalog we are happy to comply with your request. Simply send the mailing label from your catalog along with your preference to: Circulation, LASCANA, 11711 Marco Beach Drive, Jacksonville, FL 32224. Information shared with our marketing partner to deliver online display advertisements tailored to your interests will be made anonymous by a third party.

## Our legal obligations

LASCANA may also disclose information against someone who poses a threat to LASCANA's interests (such as customer fraud) or whose activities could bring harm to others.

## Other web sites

There are several places throughout LASCANA that may link you to other web sites that do not operate under LASCANA's information privacy practices. When you click through to these web sites, LASCANA's information privacy practices no longer apply. We recommend that you examine the privacy statements for all third party web sites to understand their procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing your information.

## Control access to your information

LASCANA believes that site visitors should have control over the collection and use of their personal information. You have access to your information in the following areas of LASCANA:

Your Account

The My Account page on LASCANA allows registered visitors to view and change their account settings. The e-mail settings option lets you change your e-mail address. You can change your shipping information from your account profile; update your name, phone numbers, and credit card information associated with your profile. You can also close your LASCANA account by calling: [1-888-772-3160](tel:18887223160).

## Communications from LASCANA

You will receive communications from LASCANA when you:   
• Request a forgotten password on your account  
• When you request your password, we will send your password via e-mail. All you need to enter is your  
  e-mail address.  
• Make a purchase  
• Each time you make a purchase through LASCANA you will receive confirmation of your new purchase  
  via e-mail.   
• Elect to receive special promotional marketing communications   
• When registered at LASCANA, you will occasionally receive opt-in e-mails notifying you of special promotions,  
  if you sign up for this service. Special promotional e-mails are intended to inform you of new or unique  
  swimwear or special deals that are available on LASCANA.  
• Contact LASCANA with questions/suggestions  
• When you request assistance with viewing your account, logging on to the LASCANA web site, or accessing  
  your account, we will respond to you via e-mail, live chat or telephone.

## Protecting your information

We want our site visitors to feel confident about using LASCANA to make a purchase, so we are committed to protecting the information we collect. LASCANA has implemented a security program to keep information that is stored in our systems protected from unauthorized access. Currently, LASCANA only stores the information you provide when registering at LASCANA.

Our systems are configured with data encryption, or scrambling, technologies, and industry-standard firewalls. When you send personal information to LASCANA over the Internet, your data is protected by Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to ensure safe transmission.

To verify the security of our site, look at our URL in your browser window. The letter "s" added to the "http" indicates that SSL is in effect. In your internet browsers, a closed padlock appears in the corner when you are in secure mode. Also, in many cases, your browser will warn you if you are about to send information via a site that is not secure.

## Your California Privacy Rights

If you are a resident of California, you may submit a written request to LASCANA to learn how LASCANA has shared your information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. In response to your written request, LASCANA may provide you with a notice describing the cost-free means you may use to opt-out of LASCANA sharing your information with third parties if the third party will use your information for their direct marketing purposes. If you would like to exercise your rights under California law, please send your written request to the email address or mailing address listed below. Your written request must include your mailing address so that LASCANA may provide you with LASCANA’s notice and third-party direct marketing opt-out form. LASCANA will provide you with this form within thirty (30) days of receiving your written request. 

E-mail at [email@lascana.com](mailto:email@lascana.com?Subject=Privacy%20Rights)  
Address: LASCANA 11711 Marco Beach Drive Jacksonville, FL 32224

## Changes to the Privacy Statement

LASCANA reserves the right to modify or amend this Privacy Statement at any time and for any reason. If there are material changes to this statement or in how LASCANA will use your personal information, LASCANA will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change.

Regardless of later updates, we will abide by the information privacy practices described in the Privacy Statement posted at the time you provided us with your information.

If you have questions about our Privacy Statement, please submit your questions to our Support Team!

## Contacting LASCANA

We want to make sure you have control over your online experience as a LASCANA customer, from purchasing your merchandise to protecting your personal information.

LASCANA customer service agents are ready to help with your LASCANA concerns 7am-1am EST, 7 days a week. When you need help, call [1-888-772-3160](tel:18887223160). Agents will address any questions or concerns you may have about your LASCANA purchases. We will do our best to respond to your request for assistance or other questions about LASCANA within 24 hours.

## Website Accessibility Policy

LASCANA, wants to ensure each and every customer has the best shopping experience possible, regardless of disabilities. Therefore, LASCANA will meet the World Wide Web Consortium's (W3C's) Web Content Accessibility Guidelines (WCAG) 2.0 Level AA on LASCANA.com.

If you need any assistance or have any concerns that pertain to accessibility while on LASCANA.com, please contact [1-888-772-3160](tel:18887223160) or dial 711 to obtain relay call assistance. If assistive technology is needed, please specify. This will further our effort in offering the best shopping experience possible for all of our customers.

LASCANA is located at 11711 Marco Beach Drive, Jacksonville, Florida, 32224. You may phone us at [1-888-772-3160](tel:18887223160) or you are welcome to submit your questions to our Support Team!
